

Email priyavishwas1997@gmail.com

Address

Dhayri , Pune

Phone +91-9423241407

_

Skills

Recruitment

Onboarding & Exit

Payroll Management in HRMS

Statutory Compliance

Compensation & Benefits

Performance Management

Employee Relations

Employee Engagement Activities

HR Policy Development & Documentation

Employee Safety, welfare, wellness and Health

Languages

Marathi English Hindi

Priya Vishwas Sakat

HR Professional with 7 yrs. of Experience as HR Generalist. Proficient in all aspects of Human Resource development, Recruitment Cycle. HRMS, Payroll, Operation management and Generalist Administration. Employee Relations Policy Framing and Design- Implementation. Transition management of employees from Joining to Exit formality, Internal promotion demotion, and transfer formality.

Experience

HR Manager

Anacle Systems India Pvt Ltd Pune

Sep 2023 - Present

- Consistently recruiting excellent staff for the IT company.
- Maintaining a smooth Pre and Post joining/onboarding process and induction program.
- Conducting performance and wage reviews.
- Developing HR policies and ensuring policy awareness. Handle HR Operational activities.
- Performance Appraisal.
- End to End HRMS Payroll Management and Statutory compliances.
- Attendance and Leave Management System.
- Exit formalities and FNF settlement.
- Insurance endorsements, addition-deletion data etc.
- Organizing Reward Recognition Event & Celebrating Important Days.

 Manalling Revaluation and Company and Comp
- Handling Employee grievances.
- Arranging monthly Get together and team building events.

HR Executive

Avante Codeworx Pvt Ltd Pune

Aug 2021 - Aug 2023

- HR Operational activities.
- End to End Payroll Management from HRMS
- Statutory Compliances such as PF, ESIC, PT, MLWF, Gratuity.
- Pre and Post Joining formalities of employee, Induction and training.
- Attendance and Leave Management System.
 Exit formalities and FNF settlement.
- Successfully Implemented various HR policies within the organization.
- Organizing Reward/Recognition Event & Celebrating Important Days.
- Handling Employee grievances.
- End to End Recruitment according to the company Policy.
- Participated as HR Lead in CMMI Audit.

HR Executive

Immply India Technology Pvt. Ltd Pune

Mar 2020 - Aug 2021

- Handle day to day activities.
- Recruitment according to the company policy.
- Planning and structuring of job advertisements on job portals.
- Joining formalities of employee, Induction, and training.
- Compensation & Benefits
- Performance Management
- Employee Relations.
- Employee Engagement Activities.
- HR Policy Development & Documentation.Employee Safety, welfare, wellness and Health.

HR Executive

Ace Hospital & Research Centre Pune

Jul 2018 - Feb 2020

- (Was working as HR Officer for 3 Months)
 - Recruitment, background check, qualifications, experience, job profile in consultation with concerned HOD, sourcing, budget, interview, selection.
 - Joining formalities of employee, Induction and training, including computer training and on job training. Facilitated monthly meetings to develop strategies that would positively influence workplace relationships. Created popular employee yoga and meditation classes.
 - Maintenance and updating of various registers, records, employees' personal files, leave records, Biometric attendance checking, records keeping, promotions, increments, disciplinary actions etc.
- Monthly salary processing for 100+ staffs, issue of various letter/form like Salary Certificates, FORM 16 etc., OT calculation.
- Maintenance and up dation of various registers, records, employees' personal files, leave records, promotions, increments, disciplinary actions.
- Maintain and update all data and information regarding employees at all levels, prepare MIS reports
- Process all salary changes stemming from merit increases promotions bonuses and pay adjustments.
- Created and implemented the exit and interview program process.
 Disciplinary actions including termination, show cause, suspension
- Statutory deduction such as PF, PT, Welfare and filling of International Worker, Employment Exchange, Sexual Harassment and Maternity Benefits.

Sr. Technologist HR Admin Sahvadri Hospital Ltd. Pune

Sahyadri Hospital Ltd Pune
Mar 2008 - Ian 2018

- Mar 2008 Jan 2018
- Worked on ESS and ERP, Training, orientation, Duty roaster, Recruitment & Interview,
 Leave and Attendance management.
- Leave and Attendance management.
 Held accountable for managing all the administrative & official activities while

doctor/nurses handwritten notes

maintaining the healthy work environment & discipline
HRIS,
Provide quick review of medical records and summarize the necessary

information from all the available medical records including and not limited to

Performing Paramedical Tests and assistance to the Radilogists.

Education

HR Practical Training

Jan 2018 - Jun 2018

PACE Academy Pune

- MBA (HR)

NIBM 2016 - 2017

BM Tech

Bharati Vidyapeeth Pune

2001 - 2003

B.Sc (Zoology)

Shivaji university *Phaltan* 1999 - 2001